

Amine Alliche Junior Graphic Designer

Hi, I'm Amine Alliche, a graphic designer with a passion for creating visually appealing and effective designs. I specialize in Social Media Design. In my spare time, I volunteer my design skills to several scientific clubs, including Forma Club, Openminds Club, and BioScience Club. I love being able to use my skills to support important causes and make a difference in the community. I enjoy sharing my professional experiences on social media and connecting with other designers and creatives. Let's create something amazing together!

Experience

- Graphic Designer
 Agence P4 Communication
 August 2023 Present
- Junior Graphic Designer OPTIMUS ALGÉRIE June 2023 - August 2023
- Team Leader of Senior Designers Open Minds Club July 2023 - Present
- Team Leader of junior designers Open Minds Club February 2023 - Present
- Senior Graphic Designer Open Minds Club September 2022 - Present

- Graphic Designer
 BioScience Club USTHB
 January 2023 Present
- Junior Graphic Designer Meteor Dash April 2023 - June 2023
- Design Team Leader FORMA CLUB USTHB February 2023 - March 2023
- Graphic Designer FORMA CLUB USTHB August 2022 - March 2023
- Multitasking Agent ADVANCED OFFICE June 2020 - March 2021

Education

University of Sciences and Technology 'Houari Boumediène'
 Licence in fundamental and applied genetics, Genetics
 September 2020 - July 2023

Skills

- Adobe illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe indesign, Figma, Leadership, Speaking in public, Print, Teamwork, Social networks.

Languages

- Anglais (Limited Working)
- Arabe (Native or Bilingual)
- Français (Professional Working)

Contact

00213541894532 mr.alliche@gmail.com

